Guide to the Polytechnic President's Office Records RG.042
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
Polytechnic President's Office Records
1988-2004
1995-1997
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
RG.042
1.5 Linear Feet in 1 box
Box 1
Scope and Contents
Materials are mostly media and design related including layouts for brochures and documents from the 1996-1997 Poly logo contest.
Arrangement
Original order is preserved. Constructed titles are in brackets.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open for research without restriction.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Materials were transferred from the President's Office in the Jacobs Administrative Building on 6/29/2017.
Floppy disks; Brochures; Publications; Correspondence
- Branding, 2004, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Projects, 1995-1997, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
- World Wide Web/Internet, 1995-1997, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
- [Logo contest submissions], 1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Logo, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Alum[n]us of the Month, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
- [Miscellaneous], 1988, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Leadership Seminar Series, 1994-1997 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Art, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Premises & Promises Booklet, 1992-1996 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Small Business brochure, 1994, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
- [DeGaeta Loan Brochure], 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Polytechnic University, 1995-1997, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Undergraduate Degree Programs - Electrical Eng. brochures, 1996, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Computer & Info Science Undergrad & Grad brochures, 1996, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Honors Program brochures '96 - Electrical Eng. Department, 1996, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Prelaw Program/Tech & the law, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Civil & Environmental Eng. Undergrad brochures, 1995, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Graduate Studies flyers - Civil & Environmental Eng., 1996, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
- [Artist's Rendering of 5 Metrotech], undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Campaign materials - plainspoke, 1997, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Polytechnic Fund materials 97, 1997, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Career '97 materials - Brooklyn Campus, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- [Chemical & Engineering News - 75th Anniversary Issue], 1998 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Graduate Degree Programs flyers - Electrical Eng., 1996, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Seal, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Logos - stats, 1992, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
- [Miscellaneous], 1997, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
- 9708-17 [1997 Journal Artwork] (Box 1, Folder 29)
- 1996 Journal Artwork (Box 1, Folder 30)
- 1995 Journal Artwork (Box 1, Folder 31)
- ART, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Timeline draft 1/97, 1993, 1997, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Humanities & Social Sciences Undergrad brochures, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Mechanical, Aero, & Manuf. Eng. Dept., undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Center for Finance & Technology Course Booklet, 1996, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)